My promise to you today is very simple.
If you can follow this one equation, you
will completely change your life because
you will be able to build what is the
most powerful long-term asset in today's
digital age, a personal brand. Whether
you are a parent, a teacher, a business
owner, a coach, a trainer, a
photographer, videographer, all of you
already have personal brands because it
is simply how the world perceives you.
It's your public reputation. However,
for generations before, we had to rely
on managers or bosses or clients to
advocate for us. But today, we have the
power of posting one piece of content
that can share across millions of people
exactly who we are, what we stand for,
and what we have to offer. If you can do
this effectively, you will never have to
chase another opportunity again. You
will attract them. In today's hourong
video, we will be breaking down that
exact equation. And if you can't stick
around for this entirety, then I'm
sorry. I cannot help you. You are
somebody that feels as though it's your
responsibility to change your family's
legacy. It's your responsibility to
change the outcome of where your family
will be in the future. That is how I
felt and personal branding has been the
route the medium in which that has
helped me to achieve. But I want to be
extremely clear I started exactly where
all of you are currently are at. I too
followed my favorite creators. I too
followed a creator named Christian
Guzman and he was one that I looked up
to all the time. And I would watch his
videos. I would learn about his content
strategy. And there was something deep
inside of me that I could only call a
sense of imposttor syndrome. Can you
relate to that? Or insecurity. And I had
this huge fear of being seen. And I
thought for some odd reason internally
that someone that came from the
background that I came back um and tried
to improve through could not make it.
Someone that didn't have the resources
like myself couldn't make it. I didn't
have the confidence. I wasn't an
extrovert. I had all these doubts about
why I couldn't make it. And so when I
did first start posting content, for
those that are uh very new, so the
number zero people when we were talking
about how if you're just starting out,
you probably don't know this, but if you
post content on your page and you remove
it from your main feed, it doesn't count
it as a post, right? So if you keep it
as a reals tab piece of content, it
doesn't count. But in the beginning, I
was still posting every single day. And
so when I was doing this, I was a
full-time bachelor's and masters
biomedical engineering student, meaning
that I couldn't have been in much more
of a polar opposite field. Okay? I are
there any engineers or scientists in
here? Because we are a completely
different breed. Okay, we're nerds. We
are in laboratory settings for 12 13
hours per day. And I was trying to
maximize these small pockets of time.
And although I was able to grow to a
somewhat decent size at about 4,000
followers, this is the type of content
that I was curating. And I'm actually
low-key embarrassed to show you this a
bit, but I keep it live on my page
because I want to show you that I have
started exactly where you currently are.
Let's watch together.
[music]
If you know my content now, you would
think, June, you created fashion
content. And yes, in fact, I did. And I
created fitness content. Really, in the
beginning, I was just chasing trends,
right? I just wanted to garner the
viewership. But in reality, all of these
views are very skewed, okay? Because
when you do become bigger, your views
trickle down to your original content. I
was in that 200 view count very
consistently for my first 50 posts,
right? That is where I first began in
this fashion realm and as I was chasing
these particular trends.
But at a certain point, and you can let
me know this in the chat if this
resonates with you, I personally wanted
to make meaningful content. Who in here
wants to serve people? Who in here wants
to leave an impact? Who in here wants to
make purposeful content? who in here are
sick and tired of the the dances, the
trends. You actually want to go about
making content that leaves a difference.
That was me at this particular stage.
Again, the number of posts, don't
reflect because you're on the main feed,
but I was posting every single day for
about a year and a half. I was reaching
my 10,000 followers and that's when I
decided to make a change, right? I
thought I wanted to do this the right
way. And therefore, I built a content
system. Again, I was still posting every
single day. This was probably about 2
and 1/2 years in. You can see all of the
numbers. Um, they're all live and public
and it made showing up easy, right? So,
I was still able to show up every single
day as I was maximizing these small
pockets of time as a biomedical
engineer. And ultimately, that same
system that I'm going to be teaching you
had gotten me hundreds of thousands of
new followers, ultimately millions of
new followers. So in this regard, right,
after building my content, it's one
thing to just have a number of
followers, but it's another to be able
to build a business that is aligned to
you. And so I started monetizing. I
first came out with the guide to
academic success. Then I came out with a
physical book called The Learning
System, which landed number one on
Amazon's new releases,
which skyrocketed the business to over a
million dollars while I was still a
student. Right? I remember being in my
classroom when I saw the notification
above a million. I started my own
flagship mentorship program. So I had my
biomedical engineering bachelors and
masters and then underneath that was my
concentration neuroengineering. So this
mentorship program was about human
performance centered around my
neuroengineering protocols. I became a
judge for a global entrepreneurship
competition hosted by Red Bull. You can
imagine Shark Tank on steroids. It's
where 40 different countries compete on
a national level and then you go to the
finalists in Tokyo, Japan where I was
next to AMD, Microsoft, an Olympian, a
venture capitalist firm and I was by far
the youngest judge doing exactly what I
am doing for you guys today, teaching
about personal brand. Again, who in here
wants to make good content and actually
monetize in the chat?
Good, because that's what I've done,
right? So, I have now today 8 million
followers across my platforms. I've been
able to build fun million-dollar creator
businesses. I've sold over $4 million.
I've been invited to events and travel
around the world. I'm the co-founder of
Creative College. That's what my shirt
says. And that is who's actually
sponsoring today's event. So, all of you
that are in here for free and getting
access to all this information, all the
great expertise, it's because of
Creative College. The biggest win
though, I've been able to post every
single day for the last 5 years. I went
from being a bad student to a good
student to an engineer to ultimately
entrepreneur. I have a question for
those creators that have actually some
experience creating. If you're that
person, how many of you have fallen in
the dark hole of pigeon holing yourself
into one topic because someone out there
told you to traditionally niche down and
now those content pieces may perform,
but when you post about other things, no
one actually engages, right? Yes,
definitely me me. That's because a lot
of the people out there don't actually
have the experience themselves creating
for long enough or at a high enough
level to know that that's the wrong way
of approaching it because that is common
knowledge, right? That's common what's
taught in the industry. I completely
disagree. I think having a personal
brand that has longevity is way more
important is that means it needs to
match your evolution. It needs to be
able to consist of multiple different
interests and I'm going to be sharing
you how to do that.
And what I really hope to prove to you
is that the person right in front of you
has done it time and time and time and
time again myself. I have 10 million
views. This on screen, I think there's
11 screenshots of it. I do it all the
time, right? I have consistently
millions and millions and millions and
millions of views. Even on this screen,
you're seeing almost very similar pieces
of content being reposted with the exact
news change of messaging and formatting
that I'm going to be teaching you guys
today.
Cool. Everyone excited? Because I help
creatives and entrepreneurs just like
yourselves tell your personal stories
through content formats and messaging
angles. Formats is referring to how your
content is packaged. And messaging is
simply what you're saying in your
content. Cool. And this is how I help
creators like this today, right? And
this is why I host events like this. I
am incredibly impassioned to speak on
this and to provide you guys as much as
value as I can. Okay? And I constantly
tell my story. I don't undermine or
underpin anything, right? I tell and I
show the real raw truth of how it's been
to build my businesses, to build my
content journey.
And in the last 7 months, I've
personally helped over 2,000 creators
tell their stories with the right
messaging and winning formats. These are
millions of views. 1.5 million, 6.4
million, 2.5 million, 1.4, 1.4 million,
2.6 million, 2.5 million. If you are
somebody that has interest in getting
millions of views, let me know in the
chat.
Good. All right. So, if you're new here
and you're still struggling with any of
these immediate concerns, as in you have
too many ideas, you don't want to niche
down, you think it's too saturated, that
you can't win, you don't know how to get
views on your content, it's not worth
it, I don't like selling to my audience,
please stick around for the next 3 days
because I will help you fix that mindset
and give you the strategy in which you
can immediately implement. Sound good?
Everyone sound good with that?
All right, let's do it. So, part one,
how to build the right audience. Let's
shift the mindset first.
Do you need millions of followers to be
really successful on social media?
A huge emphatic no. You're already doing
a good job in participating. Well done.
An emphatic no. Because you could have
millions of wrong followers. There are
creators that have millions and millions
of followers, but seemingly when they do
a meet and greet, nobody shows up. Or
when they launch their own products that
nobody buys. These are the wrong
followers.
What you need to do is build the right
audience. So, you're building a
community.
But how do you do that?
By understanding what content targets
your audience and by delivering it with
the right format and messaging. So,
that's why the first thing that we're
going to do in Content Insiders is teach
you the two most important topics,
messaging and formats in today's day one
event. To be very very clear with this,
a message is simply what you're saying
in that content. A format is how you are
presenting it. And if you can combine
those two, you have the content that
attracts the right audience.
Great. Okay. Awesome. All on the same
page here. You've just completed the
part one. You've understood the mindset
shift. Now, I'm going to go into a lot
of practicalities. This is where if
you're going to have your notes and your
pen and papers out, this is the time in
which you're going to be writing a lot.
All right, great. Number two, what to
post.
Everyone should draw this out for
themselves. It is your creator vision.
Again, you're going to have the
recording for this, so it's okay.
Your creator vision. And in this creator
vision, you have three parts. Your what,
who, and uniqueness. And I don't know
how to emphasize this more.
But when I get invited to speak at
events,
this is what they want me to talk about.
When a lot of your favorite creators are
DMing me and I'm helping them and they
book a call with me, they pay for it.
This is what they're asking me help for.
When I'm telling you that all those
creators that I've worked with and
they've gotten to their first million
views, this is what they point to. Do
you understand me? The creator vision is
incredibly important that we begin here
and we understand this before we move
forward. Great.
Now the first part of this is your what.
Okay. The creator vision what premise.
The what part of the creator vision is
simply your ethos. It's your message
that you want to present to the world. I
can guarantee that every single one of
you has something to offer. I guarantee
it. I guarantee, no matter how small you
think of yourself, I bet in one little
conversation, I can help you figure it
out, right? I'm going to even give you
prompts to help you figure it out. But
the truth is, if you can't do it for
yourself, [snorts] find a friend or a
family member to ask. And then I promise
you, they'll be able to tell you. Maybe
you have a great positivity about you, a
great encouragement about you, maybe
you're skilled in business, maybe you're
a good student, you have something
intangibly that your message may be
presented through content.
So, you have this overarching ethos, but
then you have three content pillars.
These can be anything of interest,
right? And then you'll have content
ideas that fit underneath each bucket.
These are going to be differentiated
from each other, as in these content
ideas will look different from this
content idea, but it all works because
you have this overarching ethos or
philosophy to connect. Let me give you
an example of mine. Hopefully, my
message has been clear since I started
today's deck. But I truly believe,
everyone in here, a personal brand is
the most valuable long-term asset that
any single one of you can build. I
believe it because you no longer will
ever have to chase another opportunity
again.
But my content pillars are different
from each other, right? So I teach about
content, strategy, storytelling,
execution. So that could be scripting,
filming, and editing. I talk about all
of those. I also talk about monetization
though, digital products, brand deals,
ecosystem, and funnels, mindset,
discipline, confidence, and growth. A
lot of creators will look at this and
think, how do you create content about
discipline and at the same time help
people with their content strategy? How
do you do that while also teaching about
funnels? It all feels very different.
Well, it's because you have this
overarching ethos. And for me, it's a
personal brand. It's the most valuable
long-term asset that you can build.
Let's look at another example here. Lean
De, one of the most popular creators on
social media today and an incredible
one. Her ethos reads, "Empowering women
to move with faith and confidence." So
she has three separate content pillars
here. Health,
fitness, running, holistic wellness,
meal prepping, faith, prayer, modesty,
mindset, journaling, healthy habits, and
discipline.
Most creators would define themselves
into one particular niche. They'll say,
"I'm a fitness creator." But Lena isn't
a fitness creator. She's significantly
more than that. She is her brand. So
that's why she can talk about prayer and
journaling and discipline all on the
same exact page and win. Does that make
sense in regards to the what portion?
This should be the most straightforward
portion of this creative vision. Great.
Awesome. You guys are doing a great job.
Take a screenshot right now. Okay. I
just gave you the three questions that I
ask every single one of my clients and
this should help you immediately deliver
upon the message or the ethos for
yourselves.
Number one, what do you want your
audience to learn, feel, or achieve by
following you? What personal experiences
shaped your care beliefs about life and
or what do you your friends or family
say about you? Number two, your
audience. So your creator vision needs a
who. The one,
how do I put this in a nice way? The one
statement that I really despise is when
somebody says something along the lines
of I'm in the 200 view jail. I despise
that one because it shows that you have
no idea what content creation is about.
If you were in a room in front of 200
people, you would be terrified. I
guarantee it. I guarantee it. If you
were in front of 200 people, you would
want to put your best
messages out. I promise it. But so many
of you get lost in numbers and forget
that they're real human beings on the
opposite side of the screen. If you have
150 people that are watching, you better
serve those 150 people to the best that
you can possibly serve them. But that
means that you need to understand who's
on the opposite side of the screen. Do
you understand me?
Good.
So, your target avatar consists of two
separate parts. One, the demographic,
and two, the psychoraphic.
The demographic is a bit more obvious,
especially if you've been creating
content for some time because your
analytics or your metric will disclose
that. What age range are you targeting?
Where are they located? What's their
profession? What's the gender breakdown?
But this is significantly more
important. So, I'm going to take a bit
more time on this. Your psychoraphic.
What is your audience currently struggle
with and what do they desire? Let me
give you a perfect example of this.
Let's look at the difference between two
types of content. And I'm going to do
this in real time with you.
Hey guys, this is why it's so important
to be disciplined
versus
if you're between the ages of 17 and 24
and you're a student struggling in your
classes, this is how you become
disciplined with this one method. Here's
another example. Content creation is is
really cool, guys. like you should try
it out versus
if you want to never chase another
opportunity again and to attract them to
have such a powerful personal brand and
public reputation. This is the method
that you need for your content. Do you
understand the difference? Right?
Immediately it's different. Right? I
didn't even try to optimize that for a
hook. I just am trying to showcase to
you the difference in who you're
actually targeting. Does that make
sense? So out of one and two, what which
one was better? Right. One and two,
which one was better? The second one.
Correct? Yes, it's so important that you
understand what your audience is
struggling with and what do they desire.
If you have no idea who to target, just
use my own younger you principle. It's
the greatest principle that helps
everyone get out of this uh rut. Just
target the version of you two to three
years younger because you had a
transformation in that two to three year
time. You know exactly what they were
struggling with and you know exactly
what they desired. Teach them, help
them, service them. Cool. This is my
example. So my demographic US and Asia
18 to 34 1:1 male to female. my
psychoraphic. A lot of creators have low
confidence. They lack clarity and focus
in their strategy. They have low
earnings. Should be very straightforward
here as well. Everyone get that? Because
this is the third branch that I'm going
to spend the most time in because it's
the most important by a long mile. Okay.
All right.
Your uniqueness is consist of three
parts. Your pain, your experience, and
your skill set. Pain is what you've
struggled with. Experience is what
you've actually gone through or what
you've developed. Skills are what are
you good at? What do people come to you
for? Right? Here's take a screenshot.
Right? Again, I I'm telling you every
single thing that I'll teach is not just
conceptual theory. It'll be all
practice. I'm going to give you prompts
to help you along the way. Do you enjoy
that? Do you like it when I give you
these prompts that allows you to
immediately implement everything that
I'm sharing and you're going to be able
to fill this out for yourself right
away. That's the practice today.
So, your pain, defining challenges,
lowest points, core insecurities,
experience, qualifications, key
milestones, who you've helped, skill,
what can you teach, mastered methods,
go-to expertise. But this is the one
area that I want to really focus on.
Okay, everyone should listen up right
here. If you are for some reason
grabbing a glass of water, if you're in
the bathroom, this is like the time in
which you should listen to me very, very
closely. Okay, I want to talk about why
it's so important for you to actually
connect to your audience.
Your most powerful content will always
be derived from your pain. Why? Because
people connect through your humanity,
not your highlights. So if you're
somebody that's constantly flexing on
your audience and you wonder why nobody
cares is because literally nobody cares,
if you can change that perspective and
think the one
universal connection that we all have is
that we struggle in our lives. And I'm
going to prove it in the next slide. If
you can use that and stop trying to
teach at your audience. Stop trying to
only be an expert. Stop trying to be
somebody that you're not. Just actually
help and relate and connect immediately
change the grand landscape of your
content creation journey. This allows
you to turn the moments in which you
might hate the most about yourself.
Right? So for me, having divorced
parents, a broken household, not being
able to have these resources, struggling
financially, all of those things were
the things I hated about myself the
most. And those became the most powerful
contents for myself. It gives it a
purpose. Now I get to service people all
across the world in that and tell people
that you're not alone.
You can help others exactly how you are
right now. You do not have to pretend to
be somebody. You are already somebody
today.
As I read one of these pains out loud,
as I go through this list, what I want
you to do in the chat is actually tell
me if you relate to any one of these.
Okay?
Have you ever had a breakup? Whether it
be romantic or whether it be friendship,
have you ever had financial hardship?
Have you ever moved alone to a different
state or to a different country
completely alone? Have you ever battled
self-doubt? Have you've ever burnt out?
Have you ever felt unseen in your
family? Have you ever been teased for
something? Have you ever had to start
over? Have you ever felt lost and
compared yourself to other people?
Everyone, take a look at the chat right
now. Do you see how many people are
saying yes? I'm showing this to you in
real time. This is what universally
people connect to. Don't forget that
that is how you will actually win and
craft a unique positioning angle in
which you can deliver upon a larger
audience at the same time a deeper
connection.
I do want to be very clear. What we're
not doing when we're telling our story
is talking negatively about other
people. It's not to say that my ex was
horrible. It's not to say my parents
sucked, but it's to highlight your own
growth. Okay? That's all we care about
your own emotional maturation from
before and after.
Do share only what you're comfortable
with and choose parts that align with
your message.
Am I clear there? This is so incredibly
important. I see people are saying this
is gold. This is Yes. Incredibly
important. Great. Okay.
And I do this every single time, right?
I tell my story over and over and over
again. And trust me when I say I didn't
start off by telling about my family at
all. My transparency for the first three
years as I grew to 300,000 followers was
telling my audience that I was a bad
student. Do you hear what I'm saying
here? You do not have to share
everything. You don't have to share
enough depth to it. No. As long as you
talk about something that has been a
struggle for you, you can turn that to
empower others. Am I clear in saying
that? So then this is the uniqueness,
right? my pain, my experience, and skill
sets as I've listed out. And then it
comes all together, right? So, you can
take a screenshot of this as well if you
want to use mine as an example. I can
move out of the way.
[laughter]
Um, and it's not necessarily all that
important how I filled it out. And
you'll see why. Because what I've done
is I spent the last literally two weeks
studying who is going to be in this
call. So, the three and a half 4
thousand of you that are in here right
now, I've done my very best to
understand what your occupations are,
right? What is your full-time
responsibility? So, if you're a trainer,
I just made you a vision. I just did it
for you. Take a screenshot of this and
use it and start working on it
immediately. Great. I'm going to move
on. Just take a screenshot if you're a
trainer. If you're a stylist, let's say
that you're in indust like industries
like fashion and beauty, take a
screenshot. I've done it for you.
Co, I literally have done the hard work
for you. Great. If you're a coach of any
kind, literally any kind, take a
screenshot of this. I've done it for
you. Okay? I'm giving you these examples
as te uh templates in which you can
build upon. All right? Even if you don't
fit one of those three demographics, I
guarantee you can take this, rearrange
it, and find your own. Does that sound
great? Does that sound helpful to you
all in terms of the creator vision?
Great. And are you enjoying this so far?
Yes, you will get the recordings. Do not
worry about that. I promise you. And
you're doing such a great job in this
call. No one is spamming. Everyone's
doing a really good job being respectful
for one another. So, fantastic.
Fantastic work. You're enjoying this is
best. Thank you. Thank you. Great job so
far. Great. This is amazing. All right.
Awesome.
Now, this is my favorite part to speak
on. It's my favorite thing to teach in
the entire world. It's learning content
formats. It's how you package your
contents.
Why should you study content? Just like
you are an engineer, you have to study
your discipline. Just like you're an
artist, you have to study your
discipline. Just like you have to study
as an aerospace scientist your
discipline. Content creation is no
different. You have to study the
formats. So I want to be extremely clear
here. You do not have to reinvent the
wheel when it comes to formats, the
messaging, everything in terms of what
to post. I just shared with it to you in
the creator vision that's inherently
yours all uniquely yours. The formats do
not reinvent the wheel. It's already out
there. You just study the formats and
you combine that with your own messaging
and then therefore you become a creator
that has high success. Does that make
sense?
Cool.
So not studying content and
understanding the formulas in them is
literally like cooking without recipes.
It's literally like building without
blueprints. It's literally traveling
without a map. Literally, right? You
you're you're wasting your time. You're
failing time and time and time again.
So, your job isn't to guess. It's to
analyze, understand, and replicate the
proven frameworks within these
successful contents.
But I want to be extremely clear. We're
studying format, not substance. You
could learn from a knitting creator,
right? Even if you're in business, you
could because we're learning formats
here. And even the most successful
knitts, like the people that knit, have
a format to their content that you can
study that is transcended across
industries. Cool.
So now when we're looking at the
different features, you don't have to
write all of these down because you'll
have the recordings for it, but we're
looking at hook, visuals and editing,
cadence, audio, story, arc, and CTA.
These are the features of the formats
that you need to study. But I've taught
this lesson hundreds of times to big
creators, to small creators, and I've
learned that there's only one way that I
can successfully teach this to the point
that it drives it home for all of you.
And it's by showing an example. Who here
wants to go through an example and we
can make this fun and interactive
together? On this next slide,
great. Great job.
I am going to play this piece of content
and I am going to try and move down like
this. And what I want you to do after
the video is done, tell me in the chat
why you think this video got 24.2
million views. Jeez Louise, this is like
mirrored. 24.2 million views.
Yeah. Okay. So, let's play the video
now.
Hold your breath.
Feel the earth move and then
hear my heartstep
[music]
away and stolen.
Let the sky fall
and it crumbles. [music]
We will stand
it all together.
When we close our truth, we will stand.
Great. I love it. I love it. I love it.
[music]
Now, everyone can tell me why they think
that video performed well.
And you can read everyone else's message
in real time. I'm seeing relatable. I'm
seeing vulnerable. I'm seeing emotional,
authentic, relatable
attitude,
emotional, motivational, inspirational,
resilience.
Okay. So, let me ask you then because
there's a lot of answers happening. If
you believe that the reason why this
content worked was because it was
relatable or vulnerable or emotional,
please say the word yes in the chat
right now.
Well, all of you that have said yes are
wrong.
And I'll explain why. If I told you,
"Hey, Beatatrice,
go and make a relatable piece of
content." That's how you went on social
media, I would be the worst coach in the
entire world. In fact, that's what most
people tell you to do online. It's
because they don't understand it. They
haven't done it themselves. That's what
they think is the reason why this video
went well, but it actually has nothing
to do with that. Because if I tell
Beatrice to make a relatable piece of
content, she doesn't have my story. How
is she going to objectively curate a
format that works well for her? She
won't know.
Instead, I am going to now list why this
video actually performed well from a
format standpoint. And I want you to
watch it once again. So, heart
connection, all of that. No, it's wrong.
So, I'll explain what the elements are
here in real time.
First, the visual hook.
That visual matches or emphasizes
what is written in text. It highlights
the emotional pain. That photo is not
from that year. And that photo was
probably not me actually unhappy, right?
It was probably me at dinner just a
little bit hungry. The photo doesn't
actually need to entail the specific
situation. It just needs to highlight
the emotion behind it. So, even if you
have no clips from you when you were
younger, it's fine. You just go and film
and take some photos of you looking less
happy. It'll work fine for what I'm
talking about. The text hook details
where the pain is from. Parents divorced
abruptly.
It's anchored in time 2013. I am not
going to make a content piece on 2013
out of nowhere, right? I'm likely going
to tell you how that reflects in the
future or how that reflects in present
day. That insinuates payoff. It
increases retention time. It ensures
that people are sticking around because
they want to see the transformation.
The text is readable. The cadence is
tight, so it's not boring, but it's not
jarring. Meaning that I can actually
read the text as it changes on screen.
I'll show you an example. I'm going to
mute this for now.
Parents divorced abruptly.
And my mom left for Korea without a
goodbye.
Struggled mentally and held a lot of
resentment. Dad did his best, but we had
our worst years financially. Does that
make sense? As in the cadence is tight,
but it's readable. So many of your
contents are way too fast. So many of
them because you're stuck on that fast
editing stuff. If the editing stop
doesn't work if it's jarring, right?
People cannot read it. They won't stick
around. So another part of this is
you'll see a border on the text. They
all have a black border to them and
they're placed in areas where it's not
too busy on the background, right? And
that's because it needs to be readable.
There's anticipatory music. It signals a
transformation.
>> [music]
>> Does that make sense? It's anticipatory,
meaning that there's a transformation.
You don't realize it when you're
watching that piece of content. You
think it's relatable. You think it's
emotional. You think it's inspirational.
It has nothing to do with that, right?
It has everything to do with the way
that you formatted your piece of
content. And that is why my students do
this type of format and win all the
time. millions of views, hundreds of
thousands of views, tens of thousands of
views. And it's not that you have to
have the same amount of clips. It's not
the fact that you have to tell my story.
You just have to match this framework
each time. One more. The call to action,
right? Encourages more follows at the
end. So, this video
alone got hundreds of thousands of new
followers. And that's because there's a
call to action there at the end. It
encourages it. The story arc is the pain
pursuit and success. I start with pain.
I start with a journey and then I go
into success. Okay. So now I'm going to
play this for you once more. And what I
want you to do is see in real time how
this actually
works
and see if you can notice it now.
Count
my heart burst
again
[singing and music]
and dream this moment.
So overdo I
swept away and stoless.
Let the sky fall
and it crumbles.
We will stand
it [music] all together. The sky falls.
I love it. I love it. I love it.
>> Do you see it now? Do you see how all of
these format features are actually what
makes that video successful? Do we
understand it now? Is everyone in this
understanding what I've just done for
you?
Nobody ever teaches you this, right?
This is how you effectively have
repeated success. And I've shown that
whether you're a small creator or a
large creator. And this is just one
format for it. It's a silent film
storytelling format that all of you can
immediately implement. All right, cool.
If you're feeling more confident, I'm
going to test you once more. Okay,
I'm going to play this and you tell me
why that this video has performed well.
Look at the
Amazing.
Wow.
>> That video always hits home for me. And
I'm going to do my very best to not get
emotional, but
do you understand it? So, let me see who
readable text, story arc, text, visual
hug. Guess what? All of you are right.
Okay. It's the exact same format.
Literally the exact same format. and you
have picked up on this right now when
you watch content you will no longer
ever see it the same way. Has that been
eye openening for you? Do you understand
what I've just done for you in real
time? I've told you what the actual
secret behind content creation is. It's
not just what the is happening. It's not
relatable. It's not the thing. It's
actually curating the format, the way
you package it, and it's objective. If
you just check these off and you're
like, I've gotten it, it's a good piece
of content. Cool. You'll never see
content ever the same again. Good. Good.
Now, I want to show you this and show
you that it's not just the silent film
storytelling format. It's not. It's
actually every single format is packaged
in a very similar way. But if you can
nail it down and study it, you
effectively
can emulate their success. I'll prove
it.
>> Second,
>> this is Maggie. She works in data
science and she actually now has her own
business. But I want to show you her
before content before she started
working with me.
>> Common pitfall carrying out an EDA
project or any portfolio project that
matters not telling a story. When a
hiring manager choose to click on your
portfolio website, each project really
only gets a few seconds of attention if
at all. So, make sure that you have a
clear header for each section and that
your storytelling is compelling and well
organized. This means you want to have a
short paragraph on your background
stories where you find your data, what
question you're
>> Whoa, well done. I'm seeing a lot of
people looking at the format and saying
what is not necessarily good for it. But
can we all agree that Maggie knows what
she's talking about? It's not like she's
spreading information that's wrong. It's
not that she's not an expert in the
field. The truth is a lot of you are
really smart but you suck at making
content because you don't know a
formatting. Right? That's the brutal
honest truth. But you can learn it. It
can be studied. And so she came to me. I
didn't tell her this. She came to me and
said, "These are the two creators that
I'm most inspired by." I said, "Let's
watch.
>> What does it take to start something?"
And by something, I mean literally
[music] anything. My first year
university prof used to always say that
the first step to doing anything is
[music] understanding the unknowns. But
how do you understand the unknowns when
you literally don't know [music] what
they are? Well, step one, list out all
the things you don't know about what it
is you're trying to pursue. And even
when that's too hard, I just throw my
ideas to Claude to get the ball [music]
rolling. So, Claude is an AI
collaborator tool. And I know AI tools
can be scary, but I think they're only
scary if you don't know how.
>> Who agrees that that's a better piece of
content? That it's a talking head, but
it's significantly more interesting.
Great. Let me show you a second example.
>> What if I told you I got $50,000 more in
salary just by negotiating? Here's how
you did it. This is lesson number 13.
Tip number one, let them give the first
number, but be prepared to take the hit.
You will get low balls. [music] Tip two,
be prepared with three numbers. Your
anchor, the highest number you'll ask
for, as my mentor once said, anchor high
like a mother. Then your due diligence
number, which is based on
>> who agrees that both of those two
content pieces from my mind and Khloe's
sheer significantly better than what she
had. This is the content that she wanted
to study. And there was one person in
this call that just put in the chat that
I'm so glad that you said this, but it
calls out the wrong understanding of
content. She said that this is going to
take too much time. It's completely
wrong. When you think that you know what
you're talking about and you try and go
and create content, that's when it takes
too long. When you just study format,
it's like a checklist. So, me and her
went together and did a piece of
content. She did. It didn't take her a
long time to make this piece of content.
Watch her new videos now.
>> Everybody thinks you need machine
learning projects in your portfolio.
Well, you don't. Here are three beginner
friendly portfolio projects that you can
use to showcase your real world data
skills. Use this Airbnb open data to
simulate AB tests. Write SQL to compare
two groups. Analyze Lyft and build a
simple dashboard like this one. Use this
311 complaint.
>> This it's not that this person has been
a crafter their entire life. She's a
normal person. Maggie is just like I am.
She learned the format. We looked at it
together and she went checklist. All
right, let me get it together. You know
what's so incredibly profound about
this? the person that she was studying
in this piece of content. Watch this
piece of content.
>> What does it take to start something?
And by something I mean,
>> who knows here Claude AI. Who knows
Claude AI here?
She now Maggie works with Claude AI is
one of the biggest creators on there in
regards to her ads. You will see it on
her page. She works with them. She gets
brand deals for them. And her ads are
the ones running all the time. Maggie's
is Maggie's is because she understood
format. Does that make sense? It's this
is the exact same message, guys. I I do
understand what I'm saying. It's the
exact same topic that she's teaching,
but the understanding of the format
completely changes how it looks.
I'm going to show you one more example.
I used to be the biggest quitter and
thought that had to do with my
depression. It actually was just my
self-doubt. So often mental health
girlies marry their depression with
their doubt when they're separate
things. One of the best things I've done
is separating the two. With myself, with
a lot of my clients, their depression
makes things really hard, isolating, and
hopeless. But it's the doubt that makes
them the quitter. Sometimes
relentlessness is this very sexy quality
of fierce self asssurance to just being
someone who will not quit on themselves.
In my more depressed girl stages, it
looks
premise here. Too long-winded. Agreed.
Right. Also, there isn't anything
visually engaging throughout the
experience. She came to me with
different craters, right? I didn't tell
her to do that. She came to me with
these craters.
>> So, it turns out that if you stop
complaining so much about things you
can't control and you start taking
control of things you can and you stop
comparing your life to other people and
you start being insanely positive about
everything,
>> she actually told me that this content
piece got 20 million plus views. And she
was asking me, "Why is it doing well? I
don't understand." I said, "Think about
the difference. Doesn't this make you
feel something different? It makes you
feel more comfortable. You make it feel
a little bit more natural. The format is
way different than you've executed. It's
not that you have to agree with every
single format that's done well, but it's
up to you to learn it, to study it. She
showed me this one as well.
[music]
Now, let's look.
>> What if you treated May like a one-mon
experiment? What if you dropped all the
weird rules that you've built in your
head and just put on a month-long alter
ego? The version of you that's
confident, that's self- assured, stay
cool, calm, collected. Because I promise
you, hesitation and fear will waste
another year faster than one month of
failure ever could. This isn't about
forcing results in a month. It's about
building that
>> complete 180. Let's watch this one.
Do we understand what's happening here?
All she's done is went from beginner to
studying formats, now understanding
exactly how to carry good content and
getting the results for it. This is
gold. I don't think you understand
exactly what's happening. Like the
people that are asking me about like, is
it the editing? You probably came in a
little bit late. What I'm trying to show
you is that it doesn't mean that you
have to spend more time. It's not about
that. It's not about you sitting there
being like, "Oh, I what should I look
like on camera or how do I No, it's like
having a checklist. It's when you study
formats. You combine it with your own
messaging and that's how you get videos
that perform well. You guys have just
seen my vision, right? My creator
vision. You will make that for yourself.
This is three different pieces of
content that I'm studying.
You can even look at these links, watch
the videos, and take my exact notes.
These are actually my own videos that
I'm studying from the past.
But what I ultimately do is I create the
7 by7 practice. It simply means seven
creators that I inspire to be like and
seven top performing videos. Meaning
that I have 49 videos that I am studying
at all times. I'm just trying to learn
what formats are working for the best
creators. I don't have to recycle their
entire content. It's just the format
that you're trying to understand. You're
trying to see how it's packaged. What's
the hooks like? What's the cadence like?
What's the story arc like? What's the
call to actions like? How are these
creators doing and learn from that? Does
that make sense what we're doing here?
Right? So, what I'm doing, and you'll
have the screen recording for this, so
you can take a look at this whenever you
want. The the actual details don't
matter, right? I show you a silent film
one, a split screen, and talking head.
And I even give you my own notes. I'm
making this as easy as possible for you.
It's completely different formats and
it's my own that I'm showing to you
right now. Cool. So, how does this come
together? It comes together and you can
literally take a screenshot of this
right now before my team kicks me off on
this. And this is how I actually plan my
content. And I think every single one of
you, if you want to know how top
creators are planning their content
effectively, this is how you have dates,
right? And you have ideas from your
creator vision and you have formats that
you've studied. So then ultimately this
is like an example of my own schedule
that I just made recently, right? My own
schedule where I'm pointing back to the
creative vision. I'm saying, "Okay, this
is from my pain. This is from my content
pillar. This is from my mindset pillar.
This is from my mindset pillar. This is
from my uniqueness skill. This is my
content pillar. This is my uniqueness
pillar and pain."
Again, does that make sense of how the
creator vision is coming together here?
Where it actually allows you to pull
ideas from. Everyone in the chat, let me
know right now before
I get I know I'm getting rushed this uh
move forward, but I just want to show
you this because I genuinely want you to
win. And this is how I do it myself and
it works.
Then the formats I'm just taking from
the things that I've studied, right?
Silent film, storytelling, b-roll,
talking head, split screen, talking
head, and I've actually showed you the
videos that come out of these. Okay? So
again, you're going to have this
recording, you'll have this resource, so
don't worry about it. But I just wanted
to give this to you as an additional
bonus. Did that make sense? Because now
you'll know exactly what content to
curate and you can actually batch it
really quickly. It'll be like uh you'll
have three videos done in 3 hours, 2
hours just because you know exactly what
you're executing upon. I want to read
through each line here and I want to ask
if this sounds like you and if a line
fits what you're currently feeling right
now, tell me in the chat. Okay. Is this
really free? Yes. You literally get the
recording and the resource 0 to 50,000
follower toolkit. It's because I
genuinely believe you deserve to win.
And you can hear it in my voice. Can you
hear my voice how impassioned I am for
this? You could hear it. It's because I
wished that somebody would have done
this for me when I first started. It
would have fasttracked my process years.
I took four years of trial and erroring,
not knowing anything about content
creation. If I can give you the
blueprint and you win and you become a
bigger creator than me, I'm proud. I'm
happy. I feel like I've done my job.
Okay. So, as each of these I read
through, I want you to tell me if you
felt that way before or you feel that
way even right now.
You were still stuck on what to post.
You have too many ideas.
You're not reaching nonfollowers, so
you're not growing as a creator.
You found some reals and YouTube videos
with advice, but it's all contradictory.
Um, not to call anyone out, but that's
what happens when you don't actually
have the experience yourself and you say
things like just make relatable content,
right? It's the people that haven't done
the work themselves to understand this,
to study it. It's those people that make
it extremely difficult for you to win.
You keep putting in effort, but you
still wonder, is this even worth it?
Right? I'm I'm doing all of this hard
work, but is this even going to have a
payoff for it?
But what you really want to do is you
want your content to actually mean
something to someone.
You want to build the right community of
real followers. You want to work with
some cool brands. You want to sell your
own products. And I know that I'm in the
way of this. I'm going to try to go like
this. You want to be loud, proud, and
bold about building something that
aligns with you. I hope every single
person says yes to that bottom one. You
want to be loud, proud, and bold about
building something that aligns with you.
You no longer want to hide. You no
longer want to have a fear of being
seen. You want to be confident. You want
to make a lot of money. You want to help
a lot of people. And you want to do that
boldly. You want to champion your own
brand just as much as an audience will
champion you.
The bridge between this and this. Your
problems right now, what you really want
to do is why I do what I do. And I'm
connecting this back to my original
story of why I'm in front of you hosting
these three days and why I have built
Creator College. Creator College is a
VIP coaching program. It allows you to
get this same type of advice and
education directly from me for four
weeks straight. If you had this type of
information for four weeks straight, let
me know in the chat. Is this your
confidence level? Would it be high or
would it be low if you had someone like
me to tell you exactly what to do for
four weeks straight? 101, right?
We are very much excited and proud of
the work that we've developed at the VIP
program. And in fact, I'm going to be
fully honest. When I launched the first
one, I had no idea how well it would do.
And I didn't think I would do a second
one, but it sold out very fast in about
a week's time. Then we did it a second
time and it sold out even quicker. Then
we did a third time. It sold out even
quicker. A fourth time and it sold out
even quicker. And then we decided, let's
build out a bigger team behind us. Let's
do the largest VIP coaching program ever
with the new complete design and we sold
out even faster. I've done this five
times. I've helped over 650 creators
myself personally. And we are now super
excited because just for those
individuals that are here today are we
announcing that enrollment is open. So
what the VIP coaching actually is, it's
just like this. But no longer will you
have your cameras and mics off. You can
talk to me in these calls. It's just you
and I will become friends. There's a
total of 41 calls about 60 to 90 minutes
long each. So there's many hours of
calls. Not only do you get the live
calls, I understand that everyone is
busy. So you will actually receive free
lifetime access to every single one of
the recordings, not just what we're
doing in the calls. So the 41 that we're
doing within the four weeks, there's
actually over 300 master classes
and 100 resources already there that
I've made that I took a lot of time
making and with my incredible team you
get for free completely for being in the
VIP program. Also, you will receive a
community to get support from our
coaches and creators. Not only that, and
this is what I'm super excited about,
and I'm actually going to show you this
here in a little bit, we made our own
AI, meaning for you guys, if you've come
into this class and listened to 70% of
it, you would be in the top 0.01% of
creators. Of course, the other 30% are
nuances, but guess what you get to do?
You get to ask it questions. So you get
to just say, "Hey, based on what June
has just said, can you give me examples
of how you would implement this format?"
You know those individuals that are
asking about, "Hey, what is formatting?
Like what does that look like?" You can
just ask it. It'll give you the exact
advice based on what we taught and
trained for. You'll also be able to work
alongside other creators who are on the
same path as you. So you don't have to
do this alone. Again, if you were doing
all of these, how easy would it be for
you to win for four weeks if you had
this directly with me and my incredible
team? Give me a rating. would be high or
low in terms of your confidence rate
that you would be successful. This is
the type of support that you get. Dr.
Jess Yao is an orthodontist from
Australia who had been trying and trying
for 2 and 1/2 years with other quote
unquote social media experts. And after
the last VIP experience, she finally
found the passion and power to share her
story. As a pure beginner from 220
followers in just four weeks, she grew
to 2221 followers and she's increasing
every single day. I will not be
surprised if she hits 10,000 followers
in the next month and a half, two
months. Right?
This is a feedback that you get. This is
Allan. He's writing a question to one of
the coaches. Look at what Veronica says,
our coach. This is an entire message
just for Allen. Do you see this? How
could you not win with this type of
feedback? And even Allan says that the
level of clarity in your feedback is
really amazing. This helps so much.
Great.
This is Kylie, a student of ours. Ask
Shhatikica a question. One of our
coaches. Shitikica answers. I answer.
Right. We're giving different types of
feedback based on what it is that she
needs help with. Personalized feedback.
Look at Nina. Another one of our coaches
sends a 9 and a half minute voice
message. Do you see this? Nine and a
half. No one else is doing that. I can
guarantee it. Nine and a half minute
voice messages. How easy would it be for
you to win?
Then Sean, who's actually going to be
teaching very soon here. He'll be
teaching you all about monetization.
He's made $300 million with the top
creators in the industry. He himself
will send you looms based on your
websites, based on your products. He
will tell you exactly how he feels about
them and give you feedback. And we don't
just help people that are already
successful. We help. We're not
discriminatory at all. We say we want to
help everyone. We truly believe that
this personal branding, June's ethos,
can actually be applied by anyone.
Literally anyone.
Martin, a pure beginner, started with
five followers and he was on private
when I first met him on private at five
followers. During this period of time,
in four weeks, in just four weeks, he
just ended with me. In four weeks, he
grew to,423 followers. Look at these
views. 180,000 views, 161,000 views,
107,000
views.
How easy would it be for you to win if
you had that type of help? And I
guarantee he's going to grow 2,000,
3,000, 4,000 as a pure beginner. Nah is
different. Nah had experience. She was a
working professional, a mom, and she had
started at 1,600 followers. We took her
in. We helped her understand exactly how
to share her story. And guess what? She
has now eclipsed 15,000 followers.
Even if you have some traction, you're
going to learn how to optimize upon it
and build even further more. Does that
make sense? How easy would it be for you
to win if you knew that you were in the
hands of people that could actually tell
you exactly what to do next? Jenna is an
example of a creator that started off
big. She started at 173,000 followers
and now she's at 308,000 followers,
selling a lot with her curriculum in
which she's helping parents. She I'm
gonna be very clear here. Every single
one of you should listen to this. She is
not only a parent, she's a full-time
teacher and she's still making content
every single day. When I tell you that
you have an opportunity to know exactly
what to do so that you can save your
time and do it efficiently, this is what
I'm referring to. Now, she has 308,000
followers and she's winning all the
time.
A lot of our students meet each other in
person. They become real life friends.
They actually want to be around each
other having people around you. And a
quick question for everyone here. How
many creators do you actually have
locally to you? Like actually who in
your friend group are actual creators,
right? None. Zero. 0000 zero z00 z00 z00
z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 z00
z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 z00 zero one
right I don't know any that's the
reality imagine being in an environment
not only do you have coaches but you
have other creators that are exactly in
the same spot as you and which you can
learn from and realize that your
struggles are not unique to you so this
is what it looks like so Veronica
started at 11,000 followers she had some
traction but she wanted to rebuild her
content strategy altogether she joined
me on calls in week one I helped her
with her creator vision the thing that
[clears throat] I just helped you guys
She received direct feedback for her
content. And in week two, she started to
grow at 11,000 views, 19,000 views,
13,000 views.
And
after following my exact advice on this
piece of content, she had 53.8,000
views. Then she grew to 12,000
followers. Then I told her exactly what
to do next.
Now she grew to 28.6,000 followers. And
today she sits around 95,000 followers.
And what's beautiful about this is that
not only did she learn while she was
with me, but she has lifetime access to
everything, guys. So, meaning that she
will have lifetime value that she could
always learn more. That is what I'm
meant passion to do. How easy would it
be for you to win if you knew exactly
what to do next? I really hope that you
enjoyed that hour-long recording from my
record-breaking free event in which we
had tens of thousands of viewers as I
was streaming for over 15 plus hours
backto backto backtoback days and that's
because I truly believe that you deserve
to win and hopefully I've helped you lay
the foundations to beginning your
personal branding journey. If you'd like
to work with myself and my team here at
Creative College, you can see the link
in the description box below.